Let's go ahead and download SB 13.
There are three.
You must be 13.
Let's configure it.
Give the name and use.
I will pick up this branch.
Under 13 are one.
A report in it.
With this branch, I'm specifying the branch here.
Okay.
So now rapport is initialized.
Now let's do the thing.
Proposing will basically download all the source code to your local.
To speed up the things, let's pass the current branch and the python thread count flags.
16.
And the download will take approximately one hour depending on the internet speed.
Porzingis now successful.
Let's start the build roster call the.
Let's build a phone emulator again to score on underscore for.
Because said it.
I think it will take at least one more night of our.
Okay.
So now the build is completed.
Let's run the emulator.
Here we go.
The emulator is now up and ready.
Let's quickly verify the build and also enable the developer options.
So here is Android 13.
Click seven times on the build number to enable developer option.